<resources>
    <string name="app_name">OCflexhelp</string>
    <string name="account_create">Dont\'t hane an account? "<b>"Create Now"</b>"</string>
    <string name="full_name">Full Name <font color='#FF0000'>*</font></string>
    <string name="last_name">Last Name <font color='#FF0000'>*</font></string>
    <string name="email">Email Address <font color='#FF0000'>*</font></string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="term"><u>Terms &amp; Conditions</u></string>
    <string name="overview">This app/website is operated by OCflexhelp. Throughout the app/website, the terms “we”, “us” and “our” refer to OCflexhelp. OCflexhelp offers this app/website, including all information, tools and services available from this app/website to you, the user, conditioned upon your acceptance of all terms, conditions, policies and notices stated here.
        \n\nBy using our app/website, you engage in our “Service” and agree to be bound by the following Terms of Service (“Terms of Service”, “Terms”), including those additional Terms of Service and policies referenced herein and/or available by hyperlink. These Terms of Service apply to all users of the app/website, including without limitation users who are browsers, vendors, customers, clients, and/ or contributors of content.
        \n\nPlease read these Terms of Service carefully before accessing or using our app/website. By accessing or using any part of the app/website, you agree to be bound by these Terms of Service. If you do not agree to all the Terms of Service of this agreement, then you may not access the app/website or use any services. If these Terms of Service are considered an offer, acceptance is expressly limited to these Terms of Service.  Any new features which are added to the current app/website shall also be subject to the Terms of Service. You can review the most current version of the Terms of Service at any time on this page. We reserve the right to update, change or replace any part of these Terms of Service by posting updates and/or changes to our app/website. It is your responsibility to check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of or access to the app/website following the posting of any changes constitutes acceptance of those changes.</string>
    <string name="general_term">1.1 By agreeing to these Terms of Service, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this app/website.
    \n\n1.2 You may not use our app/website for any illegal or unauthorized purpose nor may you, in the use of the Service, violate any laws in your jurisdiction (including but not limited to copyright laws).
    \n\n1.3 You must not transmit any worms or viruses or any code of a destructive nature.
    \n\n1.4 A breach or violation of any of the Terms will result in an immediate termination of your Services.
    \n\n1.5 You agree not to reproduce, duplicate, copy, sell, resell or exploit any portion of the Service, use of the Service, or access to the Service or any contact on the app/website through which the service is provided, without express written permission by us.
    \n\n1.6 The headings used in this agreement are included for convenience only and will not limit or otherwise affect these Terms.</string>
    <string name="hiring_ic">

    </string>

    <string-array name="country_array">
        <item>Saudi Arabia</item>
        <item>Pakistan</item>
        <item>China</item>
        <item>Oman</item>
        <item>Jordan</item>
        <item>Egypt</item>
        <item>Syria</item>
        <item>Morroco</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="time">
        <item>PM</item>
        <item>AM</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
